jobstestbd.com 2018-10-28

# Privacy Policy - Jobs Test bd

সকল চাকরির পরীক্ষার সময়সূচী ও ফলাফল মোবাইলে Notification পেতে নিচের  **Android apps**  মোবাইলে রাখেন: [Jobs  EXam Alert ](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.studyonlinebd.news&hl=en)

Thank you and be grateful to you for visiting our website [jobstestbd.com](http://jobstestbd.com/). The protection of your privacy when you use is very important to us. The publisher takes the protection of your personal data very seriously. Your data will be protected under the law. At [jobstestbd.com](http://jobstestbd.com/) we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by [jobstestbd.com](http://jobstestbd.com/) and how we use it.

The storage serves internal system-related and statistical purposes and marketing. Be recorded: name of the Internet service provider, the website from which you are visiting us and the pages that you visit, the name of the file, date, time, amount of data transferred, notification of successful download, web browser, accessing domain and the Internet Protocol address of the requesting computer. You as a user, remain anonymous.

**Information collection:**

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.

**Google Analytics:**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of www.example.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s [privacy policy here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

**  
Security of personal data:**

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

**Cookies:**

সকল চাকরির পরীক্ষার সময়সূচী ও ফলাফল মোবাইলে Notification পেতে নিচের  **Android apps**  মোবাইলে রাখেন: [Jobs  EXam Alert ](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.studyonlinebd.news&hl=en)

We use cookies to optimize the delivery of advertising on the websites they visit. Please note that it is not possible in any case to include your name, address or other personal information, either from your community account, the cookies used on your interests or out. You can of course still use our site, if you have prevented the use of cookies in your browser settings. To post comments and participate in voting, you must also accept the use of cookies.

**External Links:**

Our website contains links to other websites. You will find links on our pages that refer to pages of third parties. The publisher Nuremberg press has no influence on whether their operators comply with the data protection regulations.

**Third Party Privacy Policies:**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.jobs.LekhaporaBD.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only:**

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Use of Social Plugins:**

[jobstestbd.com](http://jobstestbd.com/) used so-called social plugins of the social network facebook.com, recordable as the “Like” button. Facebook.com is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. The plugins are marked with the Facebook logo.

**Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Consent:**

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

**For any inquiry, problems and suggestions please contact us following:**

Inform to: [jobstestbd.com](http://jobstestbd.com/)  
Mirpur 1, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Email: [jobstestbd.com@gmail.com](http://jobstestbd.com@gmail.com/)

Contact: 01720403750
